[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もっていきます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Брати з собою"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もってきます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Приносити з собою"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんぱいします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Хвилюватись"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんぱい' read in word?",
        "answer": "хвилювання"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'こたえます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відповідати"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'こたえ' read in word?",
        "answer": "відповідь"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はきけ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Нудота"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はきけがします' read in word?",
        "answer": "відчувати нудоту"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せき' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кашель"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せきがでます' read in word?",
        "answer": "кашляти"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おなか' read in word?",
        "answer": "Живіт"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'は' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зуб"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ねつ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Жар, гарячка"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'やけど' read in word?",
        "answer": "Опік"
    }
]